Resume

Name: ANUP RAVINDRA MANE

Date of Birth: 10th June 1991

Gender: Male

Communication Address: 362-363, Shaniwar Peth, Flat no. 12, 2nd floor, Neelkamal Apts, Opp.

Rasoi Dining Hall, Pune, Maharashtra, INDIA 411030

Email id: maneanup25@gmail.com

Mobile Number: 9767120730

Experience:

August 2018-May 2019 - CEO & Faculty, Chanakya Mandal Pariwar

Chief Executive Officer for 10 months from Aug. 2018 to May 2019, at Chanakya Mandal Pariwar, a non-profit organisation working for last two decades in developing professionals with global consciousness and national character.

Head of Student Enrollment, Staffing, awareness campaigns through social media and other media sources, funds raising, vendor management, working on GEMS ERP software, coordinating with teams for new ventures of the organization, compliance with Govt. Authorities, etc.

Worked with a team of 20 volunteers for managing various events, delivery of various courses,

July 2014-July 2018 - Operations Executive and Part Time Faculty, Chanakya Mandal Pariwar

Worked as a part time faculty for 4 years (2014-2018) and In-charge of Social Media, Print and Outdoor advertisement management for Chanakya Mandal Pariwar.

Worked as a sub-editor, for 6 months (January 2015-June 2015) for Swatantra Nagarik, a weekly newspaper published by Chanakya Mandal Pariwar.

Functioned as one of the Heads for managing series of eight lectures, 'Jai Bharat Jai Jagat' Part 1 in 2016, Part 2 in 2017 and Part 3 in 2018 attended by around 10,000 people daily in all 3 years.

May 2013-June 2013 - Intern, Reliance Mutual Fund, Pune

Coordinating with Cooperative Banks affiliated with Reliance Mutual Fund for sales and documentation.

Educational Qualifications:

 Pursuing Post Graduate Program in Business Analytics and Business Intelligence Course from Great Learning and McCombs School of Business, University of Texas, Austin

- Master of Business Administration in Finance (2014-Higher Second Class), Sinhgad Business School - Pune University, Pune, Maharashtra, INDIA
- Bachelor of Commerce in Cost Accounting (2011-First Class) Ness Wadia College of Commerce -Pune University, Pune, Maharashtra, INDIA
- 12th Commerce (2008-First Class), Ness Wadia College of Commerce Maharashtra State Board, Maharashtra, INDIA
- 10th (2006) P. Jog High School Maharashtra State Board, Maharashtra, INDIA

Extra-Curricular Activities:

- Participated in the 15 days, Bharat Darshan Program to travel to Northeast India (Assam, Manipur and Nagaland) and Naxalite-affected states (Chattisgarh, Odisha and West Bengal).
 This program helped us understand the culture, administration and various problems of those areas.
- Participated in an Economic status survey carried out by an NGO 'Chaitanya' which helps create
 Self Help Groups for facilitating microcredit and micro-finance in small villages based on Nobel
 Peace Prize winner Muhammad Yunus's ideas.
- Participated in Tiger census and Forest watches in Melghat Tiger reserve program under Wildlife Research and Conservation Society.
- Assisted Pune Police for the past 5 years in Ganesh Chaturthi crowd management. Incharge of the activity for 2018. During this festival, almost 100,000 people come to see the procession on the streets of Pune.

Skills:

- Interpersonal communication skills
- Better observational skills
- Command over 3 languages; English, Marathi and Hindi
- Better Conceptual understanding
- Computer skills including MS-CIT, Microsoft Office, basic desktop publishing skills

Objectives:

- To be creative and efficient in my chosen walk of life
- To be a globally competent and conscious professional

- To perform the offered task with full dedication and to the best of my knowledge
- To learn and gain as much knowledge as I can during my tenure
- Use of latest knowledge and technology to increase the performance output.

Summary:

To be creative and efficient in my chosen walk of life has always been my motto. With the varied experience I've gained from managing & executing some big events, I have trained and developed myself for performing better under pressure. This showcases my ability to perform in diverse settings and doing my best shall remain my ultimate aim.